[{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980204880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7379,"timeElapsed":36378},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980209191,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4306,"timeElapsed":40689},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980211548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2351,"timeElapsed":43047},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980217271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5718,"timeElapsed":48770},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980226043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8766,"timeElapsed":57542},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980229407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3359,"timeElapsed":60906},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980233975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4563,"timeElapsed":65474},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980240411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6431,"timeElapsed":71909},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980246872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"47","question":"Is there an age or time of your life when you felt most yourself? What was it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6457,"timeElapsed":78371},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980250762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2926,"timeElapsed":82261},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980254574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3808,"timeElapsed":86073},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980257182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2602,"timeElapsed":88681},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980259502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2315,"timeElapsed":91001},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980261203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1697,"timeElapsed":92702},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980264120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":95619},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980265549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1425,"timeElapsed":97047},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980268697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3144,"timeElapsed":100196},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980272168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3466,"timeElapsed":103667},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980277363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4209,"timeElapsed":108862},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2695,"timeElapsed":111561},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980281463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1397,"timeElapsed":112962},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980282938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1471,"timeElapsed":114437},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980284614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1672,"timeElapsed":116113},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980285957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1339,"timeElapsed":117456},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980287149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1187,"timeElapsed":118648},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980288363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1210,"timeElapsed":119862},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980289603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1236,"timeElapsed":121102},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980294379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":3911,"timeElapsed":125878},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980296605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2223,"timeElapsed":128104},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980298326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":1717,"timeElapsed":129825},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980299814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1484,"timeElapsed":131313},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980301184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1367,"timeElapsed":132683},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980302291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1102,"timeElapsed":133790},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980304221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1926,"timeElapsed":135720},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980305288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1061,"timeElapsed":136787},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311047,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5756,"timeElapsed":142546},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"166","question":"Were you ever in a school play? What was your role? What was the plot of the play?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4043,"timeElapsed":146594},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5099,"timeElapsed":152766},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980322853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1582,"timeElapsed":154352},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980324632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":1774,"timeElapsed":156131},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3303,"timeElapsed":159439},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980329267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1323,"timeElapsed":160766},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1176,"timeElapsed":161947},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980331602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1150,"timeElapsed":163101},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980332654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1046,"timeElapsed":164153},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980333788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1128,"timeElapsed":165286},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980339254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4637,"timeElapsed":170753},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2112,"timeElapsed":172869},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980343424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2050,"timeElapsed":174923},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980345471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2042,"timeElapsed":176969},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4000,"timeElapsed":180973},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980351389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1911,"timeElapsed":182888},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980352618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1225,"timeElapsed":184117},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4284,"timeElapsed":188406},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980359436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2524,"timeElapsed":190934},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980364484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4120,"timeElapsed":195982},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980366556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2068,"timeElapsed":198055},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2453,"timeElapsed":200513},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2521,"timeElapsed":203038},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":1130,"timeElapsed":204172},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980376331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3652,"timeElapsed":207830},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980377657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1322,"timeElapsed":209156},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980378992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1332,"timeElapsed":210491},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980381388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"245","question":"What is the most sophisticated piece of technology or machinery you understand? How did you learn about it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2392,"timeElapsed":212887},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5152,"timeElapsed":218959},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2589,"timeElapsed":221552},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980392878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2820,"timeElapsed":224377},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2563,"timeElapsed":226943},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398843,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3395,"timeElapsed":230342},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2916,"timeElapsed":233262},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980403869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2102,"timeElapsed":235368},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1562,"timeElapsed":236935},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980407831,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2389,"timeElapsed":239330},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1292,"timeElapsed":240626},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980416411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6379,"timeElapsed":247910},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2638,"timeElapsed":250551},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980420269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1213,"timeElapsed":251768},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3076,"timeElapsed":254847},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1437,"timeElapsed":256289},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980425857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1063,"timeElapsed":257356},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1054,"timeElapsed":258415},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980428005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1086,"timeElapsed":259504},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"215","question":"Is there anybody (a famous person or someone you know) that you’ve learned to do an impression of? How did you learn this? Who did you most recently show this to?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1203,"timeElapsed":260711},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5614,"timeElapsed":267264},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1822,"timeElapsed":269091},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":2581,"timeElapsed":271676},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2107,"timeElapsed":273788},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2860,"timeElapsed":276652},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1213,"timeElapsed":277871},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980447672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1296,"timeElapsed":279171},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1207,"timeElapsed":280381},{"subjectID":"7dbvug4693","prolificID":"5f7896d1be4d8242ef2236c6","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2400fdc5fcf05fba6f6","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980449991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1104,"timeElapsed":281490}]